<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>The Gooberati</title>
    <description>In which we describe our travels in Italy.
</description>
    <link>http://yourdomain.com/</link>
    <atom:link href="http://yourdomain.com/feed.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/>
    <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2015 21:56:17 +0100</pubDate>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2015 21:56:17 +0100</lastBuildDate>
    <generator>Jekyll v2.5.3</generator>
    
      <item>
        <title>Unprepared for Italy</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;Because we were so occupied with planning our wedding, and finding decent accommodations in Rome and Tuscany, we didn’t put any real thought into what we would actually do on our honeymoon until we stepped off the plane. It was a bit like the dream in which you walk into a final exam realizing you never went to class.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;On our first day, after trying to beat our jet-lag with a four-hour afternoon nap (maybe not the best idea), we had an amazing dinner at Cucina de Enzo, a small restaurant on one of the crooked back streets in Trastavere. The next night we had drinks at the rooftop bar of the Hotel Forum, which overlooks a small section of the ruins (if you stand in one corner of the bar) and otherwise offers a nice view of the night sky and the planes lined up to land at Fiumicino. The drinks were excellent. By a lucky coincidence, we passed back through the Forum just as the city was offering nighttime tours, complete with a slightly hokey audio guide, and a light and moving images projected onto the ruins to illustrate what they might have looked like in ancient times.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;The next two days, Thursday and Friday, we saw the Capitoline and Vatican Museums, both of which are amazing. Still hobbled by jet lag, we arrived late to the Vatican Museum, at around 4, meaning there was no line at the door and no crowds inside, not even in the Sistine Chapel, where we moved around freely and even sat on one of the benches against the wall. Two days later we took the train to Ostia, the ancient port city on the outskirts of Rome, where our late arrival (jet lag can be hard to beat sometimes) meant the setting sun cast the ruins in a cinematic glow. Just down the street from the ancient city we found a nice restaurant on the street and had yet another delicious meal.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;Now we are in Tuscany, in a converted hay barn outside the small hill town of Castelnuovo Berardenga, on the property of a couple from Milan who decided to become Tuscan vintners and olive oil makers in their retirement years. They have a big white dog that barks in the early evening and outside, at night, you can clearly see Orion, not only his belt but his drawn bow and bent knees. He stands just below the chalky white Milky Way, which spills across the sky.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;We still don’t know what we will do tomorrow. Luckily, however, a honeymoon is not a test, and it’s ridiculously easy to have a great time in Italy, even if you haven’t cracked a guide book or looked up anything on the internet before you hand your passport to the customs officer.&lt;/p&gt;

&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&quot;/assets/templeofvenus.JPG&quot; alt=&quot;Temple of Venus in the ancient Roman Forum&quot; /&gt;&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/update/2015/11/03/title.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/update/2015/11/03/title.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
      <item>
        <title>First Post</title>
        <description>&lt;p&gt;We’re married, so we’re blogging together now.&lt;/p&gt;
</description>
        <pubDate>Sun, 01 Nov 2015 00:00:00 +0100</pubDate>
        <link>http://yourdomain.com/update/2015/11/01/first-post.html</link>
        <guid isPermaLink="true">http://yourdomain.com/update/2015/11/01/first-post.html</guid>
        
        
        <category>update</category>
        
      </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
